[{
  "options": [
    "to ring",
    "to find",
    "to hid",
    "to call",
    "to read"
  ],
  "question": "«To lose» сөзінің антонимін табыңыз.",
  "answer": "to find",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "isn’t he",
    "isnt’t my father",
    "does he",
    "does my father",
    "is he"
  ],
  "question": "Дұрыс жауабын таңдаңыз:\nMy father is from Astana, ….?",
  "answer": "isnt’t my father",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "етістік",
    "герундий",
    "зат есім",
    "үстеу",
    "жалғаулық шылау"
  ],
  "question": "Берілген сөз қай сөз табына жатады?\nEvolution",
  "answer": "зат есім",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "I think it don’t work",
    "Doesn’t play with a book",
    "She doesn’t fond of the classical music",
    "Tom don’t like reading a book",
    "I don’t have much money"
  ],
  "question": "Дұрыс құрылған сөйлемді көрсетіңіз.",
  "answer": "I don’t have much money",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "Vowel",
    "Consonant",
    "Adjective",
    "Verb",
    "Noun"
  ],
  "question": "Кері мағынасы бар сөзді табыңыз:\nCat",
  "answer": "Adjective",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "a",
    "an",
    "the",
    "some",
    "none"
  ],
  "question": "Which article is used before the word 'umbrella'?",
  "answer": "an",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "an",
    "a",
    "the",
    "some",
    "none"
  ],
  "question": "Which article is used before the word 'apple'?",
  "answer": "an",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "in",
    "on",
    "at",
    "to",
    "from"
  ],
  "question": "Choose the correct preposition:\nI usually go to bed ____ 10 o'clock.",
  "answer": "on",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "for",
    "with",
    "to",
    "on",
    "at"
  ],
  "question": "Choose the correct preposition:\nI'm angry ____ you because you broke my toy.",
  "answer": "for",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "none",
    "whom",
    "who",
    "whose",
    "which"
  ],
  "question": "Choose the correct relative pronoun:\nThe girl ____ brother is a doctor.",
  "answer": "who",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "is",
    "are",
    "were",
    "am",
    "been"
  ],
  "question": "Choose the correct form of the verb 'to be':\nThe students ____ listening to the teacher.",
  "answer": "are",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "a",
    "an",
    "the",
    "some",
    "none"
  ],
  "question": "Choose the correct article:\nThere is ___ orange on the table.",
  "answer": "an",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
},{
  "options": [
    "at",
    "on",
    "in",
    "from",
    "to"
  ],
  "question": "Choose the correct preposition:\nShe is waiting ____ the bus stop.",
  "answer": "at",
  "__v": 0,
  "dependent": "eng1"
}]
